<cv>

<personal-details>
	<name>Faith</name>
	<phone>07432670559</phone>
	<email>faith.kareber@hotmail.com<email>
</personal-details>

<bio>
	Hardworking and reliable BSc (Hons) Computing graduate. An organised and committed worker who gives due attention to any task, big or small. A confident and a very able worker who can excel in a busy environment; especially enjoys being part of a team from experience working within a fast-paced restaurant. A capable person who is willing to learn new skills and adapt to various methods of working.

	My passion for assisting others, outstanding customer service, excellent communication skills and problem solving makes me the perfect candidate for working within the IT field.
</bio>

<work-history>

	<oganisation>Lola Events Staffing</organisation>
	<role>Hostess</role>
	<date>2015-2016</date>
<role-description>
	Duties include meeting, greeting and engaging with guests at prestigious client events and 5 star hotels. I have worked at a range of exceptional hotels and events some of which include; The Shard – Shangri-la Hotel, Marriot hotel, Grosvenor hotel, Rosewood hotel, Westminster Plaza hotel, Santander Investment banking event, Pride of Britain Awards and London Bierfest.

	Hostessing has given me the greatest opportunity to meet and engage with high profile and high net-worth individuals who have given me exceptional advice into achieving my goals. 
</role-description>


<oganisation>Dialogue by Designer</organisation>
	<role>Junior IT Project Officer</role>
	<date>2014-2015</date>
		<role-description>
				My role included working alongside senior members of staff to set up IT infrastructure to support project specific requirements. This often involves customising in-house application, websites, and databases on which our consultations are built. Projects worked on include: National Grid North West Coast Connections, Horizon Nuclear Power, NHS CHD and many more. Technologies used within this role include: SQL Server 2005, Microsoft Access and Visual Basic.
		</role-description>



<oganisation>Mcdonalds</organisation>
	<role>Crew member</role>
	<date>2012-2014</date>

</work-history>

<education-history>
	<uni-name>University of Greenwich</uni-name>
	<course>Bsc(Hons)Computing</course>
	<duration>2012-2015</duration>
</education-history>

</cv>
